<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>coiniovas</title>
    <link href="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/." />
    <updated>2018-05-27T18:16:13+04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>amjad</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/.</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Should you be concerned about GDPR</title>
        <author>
            <name>amjad</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./introductory-post-copy.html"/>
        <id>https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./introductory-post-copy.html</id>

        <updated>2018-05-27T18:15:28+04:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./media/posts/2/" alt="" />
                <div>If you have or use any of the following items on your website, then it will be worth double-checking that you meet the requirements of the GDPR before the May deadline</div>
<ul>
<li>Your website collects data on visitors, such as via Google analytics. Your site has a registration form.</li>
<li>You have e-commerce functionality on your site; that is, you collect information to process payments, orders etc.</li>
<li>You have a newsletter sign-up form.</li>
<li>You include social media links on your pages e.g. Facebook, Twitter etc...</li>
<li>You use a comments system for your articles, such as Disqus.</li>
<li>Your site has scripts that use cookies.</li>
<li>You have a contact form for users to get in touch.</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Introductory Post</title>
        <author>
            <name>amjad</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./introductory-post.html"/>
        <id>https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./introductory-post.html</id>

        <updated>2018-05-27T13:09:05+04:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://amjad-desai.github.io/Publii/./media/posts/1/" alt="" />
                <div>Data handling</div>
<div class="align-left">Customers now have a ‘right to be forgotten’ so that they can have their
<div class="gallery" contenteditable="false" data-is-empty="true"> </div>
details removed from a website and the database if they request it. Webmasters should therefore have a process in place that caters for this and also facilitate a way that users can request this, whether it mentioning it clearly in their privacy policy or elsewhere on the website.</div>
<div> </div>
<div>To emphasize the security of customer data, website owners are required to keep all data secured in an encrypted environment. By adding an https protocol to your website, you are helping encrypt the data that customers fill on your site.</div>
<div> </div>
<div> </div>
<div>GDPR rules highlight that all data must be stored in the EU. Whilst this can be tricky using operations and software based in the US and overseas, it is important to check that these companies are GDPR compliant whether you are working with GoDaddy, Wordpress, Google, Zoho or Mongodb.</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
